How to make a magic sticker
Now, let's make the magic sticker details of this jacket.
Next, let's introduce the method of using the board to show this detail.
Sew the magic sticker in the form of a board on the costume.
In order to show the material of the magic sticker,
you need to apply a new fabric to the magic sticker board.
Add the fabric to the pattern that we have processed into four consecutive patterns.
Add the fabric texture of the magic sticker here.
Automatically generate the corresponding hair line sticker.
And adjust the strength of the hair line according to the need.
Change the physical attribute to hard and sticky.
Adjust the thickness of the fabric according to the need.
You can also increase the thickness of the fabric to show the thickness of the magic sticker.
So our magic sticker fabric details are ready.
Then we make the magic sticker face details.
First,
let's make the magic sticker face details.
Then we can copy the fabric of the magic sticker.
By modifying the pattern,
we can get a face of the magic sticker.
Second,
add the sewing line to the face of the magic sticker.
After adding the card to the inside,
open the simulation.
It can help us quickly arrange the card and stabilize the simulation.
Finally,
we can match the other side of the card and copy it out.
You can use the sewing line.
The sleeves are Keiko and the magic sticker are sewn together.
The performance is consistent.
It can also be fixed withNO sewing needles.
So our magic sticker details are finished.
Thank you.